https://www.infinish.com/index.php/privacy-policy/

Contact Information
At Infinish we take our customer's privacy seriously. We believe that providing complete confidentiality with any of the information we receive on the telephone or through this web site is an essential part of maintaining a high level of integrity and earning customer trust. For this reason and many others, we will not under any circumstances use confidential or personal information provided to us for any other purpose than to process and ship orders. To keep this information secure we have implemented the highest level of encryption available on our entire website as well as for any data that is stored on our web server.
Please read this document in its entirety. If at that point you decide you still need further information than what is listed here, feel free to contact us and we will be glad to address any additional questions or concerns you may have.
Top
The following information lists in detail;
What personally identifiable information Infinish collects.
What personally identifiable information third parties collect through this Web site.
What organization collects the information.
How Infinish uses the information.
With whom Infinish may share user information.
What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Infinish control.
Top
Information Collection
Infinish, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on infinish.com. Infinish collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.
Top
Orders
We request information from the user on our registration and checkout pages. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date). This information is used only for billing purposes and to fill the customer's order. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.
Top
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. As we do not currently require users to login we use only persistent cookies to store order data. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.
We use persistent cookies to store the cart's contents on the user's computer for the convenience of completing orders and checking out at a later date, this is the only reason for the use of cookies at infinish.com.
Top
Log Files
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use a tracking utility called webalizer that uses log files to analyze user movement, these reports are used exclusively to help us in decisions regarding improvements to this web site. No personal information is acquired with this utility.
Top
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.
Top
Third Party Intermediaries
We use multiple carriers to ship orders and use Authorize.net and Chase Paymentech for credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Top
Business Transitions
In the event Infinish goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via E-mail in addition to a prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. At that time customers will be given the choice to leave confidential data they have decided to keep on file with us for future transactions or have it destroyed.
Top
Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that infinish.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Top
Security
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.
When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or other billing information), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption available in the industry - EV SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon in the address bar of Web browsers such as Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open when users are just 'surfing'. When the lock or address bar changes to green in color this means that the page and data are secured using EV or extended validation and the highest level of security availble. More information about SSL can be found here: SSL Explained
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, and any sensitive data is encrypted there as well.
If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users are welcome to call or send us an e-mail.
Top
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Top
Contact Information
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
